bonnieplants.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy – Bonnie Plants

## Bonnie Plants, Inc. and its affiliated companies (“Bonnie Plants”) gather certain types of information from visitors. We are providing this privacy policy to help you understand the types of information we gather, how it is used and shared, and how you can update or modify user profile or registration information you have provided to us online. This policy applies only to information collected online at bonnieplants.com and other sites and mobile applications where this policy has been linked (collectively, the “Bonnie Plants Websites”).

## Information Collected

  * General Browsing Information: Any time you visit the Bonnie Plants Websites, we may gather certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons. This information includes browser characteristics, your service provider IP address, the search engine you may have used to locate the Bonnie Plants Websites, a unique device identifier, device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, information on actions taken on a Bonnie Plants Website, and dates and times of visits.
  * Personal Information Voluntarily Provided: We gather personal information you provide to us (such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, demographic information, payment information) when you request information about a product or service, register on the Bonnie Plants Websites, request email reminders or email newsletters, sign up for a service, enter one of our sweepstakes or contests, take a survey or use any of the other interactive portions or features of the Bonnie Plants Websites. When personally identifiable information is requested on the Bonnie Plants Websites, some requests are marked as “Required”; this personally identifiable information is necessary to allow you to participate in the feature or service you’ve requested.
  * Information Provided by You Relating to a Job Opportunity: If you elect to voluntarily create a job interest profile through the Bonnie Plants Websites to show interest in a job opportunity with Bonnie Plants, you will be providing your name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address and information with respect to work experience, educational background, position sought and at your option, the information contained in your resume.

## How Your Information Is Used

We use the information collected at the Bonnie Plants Websites for the following purposes:

  * To understand your needs and preferences, to develop, market, sell or provide products and services, and possibly to conduct surveys, research and evaluations.
  * To complete your request for services or respond to your use of features on the Bonnie Plants Websites.
  * To tailor your experience on the Bonnie Plants Websites to your interests and geographic region.
  * To respond to your inquiries about our products and services.
  * To inform you of special events and offers or programs offered with our selected companies and marketing partners.
  * To operate, evaluate, manage, improve and develop Bonnie Plants’ business and operations, administer accounts, collect and process payments.
  * To perform data analytics.
  * To detect and protect Bonnie Plants and other third parties against error, negligence, fraud, theft and other illegal activities and to audit compliance with policies.
  * As permitted by, and to comply with, any legal or regulatory requirements.
  * Any information you provide to us about your interest in a job opportunity at Bonnie Plants will be accessed by Bonnie Plants personnel for the purpose of considering, and possibly responding to, your interest in Bonnie Plants and for planning and monitoring our recruitment campaigns.

In addition, we use information collected through cookies, web beacons and other automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users’ visits to Bonnie Plants Websites, (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users’ interests and the manner in which our users browse the Bonnie Plants Websites, and (iii) managing our business. We may supplement data we collect on the Bonnie Plants Websites through automated means with information about your location (such as your zip code) to provide you with content that may be of interest to you. We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, and administer the Bonnie Plants Websites, identify users of the Bonnie Plants Websites, and gather demographic information about our users. We use clickstream data to determine how much time users spend on the Bonnie Plants Websites, how users navigate through the Bonnie Plants Websites, and how we may tailor the Bonnie Plants Websites to better meet the needs of our visitors. We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

## Disclosure of Personal Information

We collect and maintain the personal information of our consumers for the use of Bonnie Plants and our marketing agents. We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties, and do not share or trade your personally identifiable information with third parties other than as described below.

  * Selected Companies: Bonnie Plants may work with select retailers and other companies at various times to provide expanded services that relate to Bonnie Plants Websites or its visitors. As part of such a relationship, Bonnie Plants may share with these companies or these companies may interact with your browser, collect or have access to some or all of the information collected in connection with certain interactive functions offered on the Bonnie Plants Websites or on other web sites where Bonnie Plants provides advertisements and interactive functions.
  * Service Providers: Bonnie Plants may use other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include administering e-mail services, marketing, monitoring website activity and running special promotions, such as sweepstakes, contests or surveys. Such parties only have access to the personal information needed to perform these functions and may not use or store the information for any other purpose.
  * Business Transfers: In the event that Bonnie Plants sells or transfers a particular portion of its business assets, consumer information may be one of the business assets transferred as part of the transaction. If substantially all of the assets of Bonnie Plants or its brands are acquired, consumer information may be transferred as part of the acquisition.
  * Compliance with Law/Safety: Bonnie Plants may disclose specific personal information based on a good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to comply with or conform to the law or that such disclosure is necessary to protect the users of the Bonnie Plants Websites, the website itself, or the public.

## Retention of Personal Information

Bonnie Plants may retain the information it collects on the Bonnie Plants Websites as long as necessary to accomplish the purpose for which the information was collected. In some cases, Bonnie Plants is required by law to retain the information it collects for a specified period of time.

## Policies on Children

To ensure compliance with federal law, Bonnie Plants does not knowingly collect or maintain information provided by children under the age of 13.

## Use of Cookies

Bonnie Plants may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small text files that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. Both we and others (such as our service providers and advertising networks) may collect personal information about our visitors’ online activities over time and across third-party websites. Bonnie Plants Websites are not designed to respond to “do not track” signals received from browsers. We use cookies to offer you the convenience of not having to reenter information, and provide you with information targeted to your interests. A web beacon, also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Through these automated collection methods, we obtain “clickstream data,” which is a log of content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website or using an app. As the visitor clicks through the website or uses an app, a record of the action may be collected and stored. We may link certain data elements we have collected through automated means, such as your browser information, with other information we have obtained about you to let us know, for example, whether you have opened an email we sent to you. You may modify your browser settings through the “help” section of the toolbar to disable the use of cookies. Please note, by doing this certain features on our website may not function correctly and you may be required to re-enter your information more frequently. We may use third-party web analytics services on the Bonnie Plants Websites, such as those of Google Analytics and Site Survey. These service providers help us analyze how users use the Bonnie Plants Websites. The information collected for this purpose (including your IP address and other information collected by automated means) will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers. To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. The providers of third-party apps, tools, plug-ins and widgets on the Bonnie Plants Websites, such as Facebook “Like” buttons, also may use automated means to collect information regarding your use of the websites and apps and your interactions with these features. This information is subject to the privacy policies or notices of these providers.

## Interest-Based Advertising

On Bonnie Plants Websites, we may collect information about your online activities for use in providing you with advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests. This section of our Privacy Policy provides details and explains how to exercise your choices. You may see certain ads on other websites because we participate in advertising networks. Advertising networks allow us to target our messaging to users through demographic, interest-based and contextual means. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs and web beacons. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that may be tailored to your individual interests. The information our ad networks may collect includes information about your visits to websites that participate in the relevant advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the websites. This data collection takes place both on our websites and on third-party websites that participate in the ad networks. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. To learn how to opt out of this advertising networks interest-based advertising, please visit the consumer opt-out page at Digital Advertising Alliance at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## Accessing Bonnie Plants Websites from Outside of the United States

If you are visiting the Bonnie Plants Websites from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States. Any information you provide during your visit will be processed and maintained on our Web server and/or other internal systems located within the United States.

## External Links

The Bonnie Plants Websites contains links to other sites that are not a part of Bonnie Plants. Bonnie Plants is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. To help ensure the protection of your privacy, Bonnie Plants recommends that you review the privacy policy of any site you visit via a link from the Bonnie Plants Websites.

## Passwords

To access registration information that you create on the Bonnie Plants Websites, you will need to use a password that you create. To protect the integrity of the information contained in this record, you should not disclose or otherwise reveal your password to third parties. If you forget your password, click on “forgot password” in the login screen and we’ll send you an e-mail with a link to a unique URL, where you may change your password.

## Public Forums

Bonnie Plants may make blogs, chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users at various times on the Bonnie Plants Websites. Please remember that, unless otherwise stated, any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas (including uploading photos into these areas). Bonnie Plants has specific terms of use for these features and you must agree to comply with these terms of use prior to your initial use of these public forums.

## Correcting and Updating Information

You can update or modify your registration information if you elect to register with a Bonnie Plants Websites by logging into your registration information and following the instructions provided to update or modify such information.

## Updates to Privacy Policy

This privacy policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Bonnie Plants Websites. Should there be a material change to our information collection or use practices, the change will be applied only to information collected on a going forward basis and the “Effective Date” of the policy will be updated.

## Security Statement

Bonnie Plants takes your privacy seriously and values its relationship with you. Bonnie Plants will take reasonable physical, technical and organizational measures to safeguard and secure any personal data you provide to us.

## Your Options

You may always discontinue your receipt of future email newsletters and/or other email communications you previously requested from Bonnie Plants. To change what email communications you receive from Bonnie Plants follow the unsubscribe instructions in the applicable email communication or contact Bonnie Plants customer service at [http://bonnieplants.com/contact-us/customer-service](https://bonnieplants.com/contact-us/customer-service/). To learn how to opt out of this advertising networks interest-based advertising, please visit the consumer opt-out page at Digital Advertising Alliance at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## Contacting Bonnie Plants

If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, you may contact us at:  
Bonnie Plants  
Attn: Customer Service  
1727 Hwy 223  
Union Springs, Alabama 36089

###### Effective Date: October 7, 2016
